William Lescaze Papers
William Lescaze Papers
1915-1969
Lescaze, William, 1896-1969.
65.0 linear ft. (ca.)
Papers of the American international style architect. Correspondence, and architectural drawings, designs, and specifications related to Lescaze's clients, which included the Philadelphia Saving Fund Society and Columbia Broadcasting System. Also included are biographical materials, lectures, photographs, writings, and material related to Lescaze's one-time partner, George Howe.
148789
Biographical History
William Lescaze (1896-1969) was a Swiss-born American architect, known as one of the pioneers in modernism in American architecture.
Born March 27, 1896 in Geneva, Switzerland, Lescaze studied architecture at the Ecole Polytechnique Federale in Zurich. He received his Master of Architecture in 1919, went to Paris, and worked briefly in the war-devastated areas of France before coming to the United States in 1920. He became a US citizen in 1929.
Lescaze worked initially for Hubbell & Benes in Cleveland, Ohio, but in 1923 moved to New York City and opened his own firm. In 1929 he entered into partnership with George Howe and established offices in New York and Philadelphia. In 1933 Lescaze married Mary Connick Hughes, with whom he had one son, Lee Adrien. In 1934 he re-established the firm under his own name and directed it until his death in 1969.
Among his earliest workds were a country house/hunting lodge for Comte Jean de Sieyes (Job #220), the nursery for Oak Lane Country Day School (Job #258), and soon afterwards the 33-story Philadelphia Savings Fund Society building (Job #284). In 1933 he designed his own town house and office in East 48th Street (Job #602), and in 1938 the California headquarters of the Columbia Broadcasting System (CBC) in Hollywood (Job #515). His work with low-cost housing led to his appointment as senior architect for the Williamsburg (Ten Eyck) houses in Brooklyn (Job #388).
From 1949 to 1959 Lescaze served on the New York State Building Code Commission, and in 1951 he was named a Fellow of the American Institute of Architects.
His later work included the City and Municipal Courts Building in Manhattan (Job #1000), the Swiss Chancellery in Washington, DC (Job #1057), the Brotherhood House at 7th Avenue and 40th Street (Job #1108), the Church Peace Center at the United Nations Plaza (Job #1183), the 777 3rd Avenue building (Job #1194), the Chatham Plaza Center in Pittsburgh (Job #1284), the 1 New York Plaza Building (Job #1306), and One Oliver Plaze (Oliver Tyrone Building) in Pittsburgh (Job #1330).
An essay by Christian Hubert written to preface a 1982 exhibition catalog, and which places Lescaze in the history of modern architecture, has been copied as an appendix to this guide.
Lescaze was the author as well as the subjet of numerous essays, articles and reviews in both professional and popular journals. He spoke frequently and appeared on radio broadcasts often. Major early essays include his "A Community Theatre" in Edith J.R. Isaacs' Architecture for the New Theatre (New York, 1935), and his contribution to Augusto Centeno's The Intent of the Artist (Princeton, 1941). His book On Being an Architect appeared in 1942; a copy of this work is available in the Rare Book Collection, as are copies of the two major pieces of Lescaze scholarship to date, namely Lorraine Welling Lanmon's William Lescaze, Architect (doctoral dissertation, University of Delaware, 1979) and William Lescaze, published by the Institute for Architecture and Urban Studies and Rizzoli International Publications. (New York, 1982).
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The William Lescaze Papers consists of biographical material, correspondence, drawings (renderings, sketches, etc), photographs, photo panels, slides, and other formats. It has been divided into ten series; items relating to a given project may therefore be found in several series; the researcher is advised to review the entire finding to ensure locating all relevant material.
Individual commissions contains blueprints, drawings (renderings, sketches, etc), photographs, photo panels and other formats relating to specific commissions executed by Lescaze either alone or in partnership with George Howe. Commissions without numbers are listed first, followed by numbered commissions.
Material relating to Lescaze's Architectural career consists of a comprehensive job listing, and school and miscellaneous material.
Biographical material contains biographical sketches and chronologies, resumes, exhibit lists, lectures and radio broadcasts, memberships and appointments, and a list of works executed.
Correspondence is entirely incoming, apart from one letter to the editor from Lescaze. Correspondents include academic institutions (Columbia, Harvard, Princeton), museums and galleries (Cincinnati Art Museum, Museum of Modern Art), publications (Architectural Review, New Republic), and individuals (Le Corbusier, Mabel Dodge Luhan, Pierre Soulages).
Drawings contains a selection of architectural drawings but also a number of industrial design drawings, such as designs for ashtrays, lamps, radiators, and so forth, plus some etchings and sketches.
Legal and financial papers include contracts, leases, passports, naturalization papers, and Lescaze's Swiss military service records.
Memorabilia includes certificates and awards, cards, photographs, printed material, and scrapbooks.
The Architectural works series contains material specifically relating to particular architectural projects. ranging from Ansonia High School to the Woods End apartments.
Writings contains primarily of works by Lescaze. There is a copy of his On Being an Architect as well as lectures, radio interviews, notes, and other material. There are also a few items by others, about Lescaze.
Arrangement of the Collection
Commissions are arranged in order by commission number, with unnumbered and unidentified commissions listed first. All other series are arranged alphabetically.
Related Material
See the "Howe and Lescaze Buildings Map" at http://www.greatbuildings.com for locations and photographs of Lescaze's buildings.
Subject and Genre Headings
Architects; Lescaze, William, 1896-1969.; Howe, George.; Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.; Philadelphia Saving Fund Society.; Architectural design.; Architectural drawing -- United States -- 20th century.; Architectural firms.; Architectural practice.; Architecture -- United States.; Architecture -- Designs and plans.; Architecture -- Details.; Architecture, American.; Architecture, Domestic -- United States.; Architecture -- United States -- 20th century.; International style (Architecture) -- United States.; Swiss Americans.; Architectural drawings (visual works); Blueprints (reprographic copies); Correspondence.; Interviews.; Lectures.; Photographs.; Architects.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of William Lescaze and Mrs. William Lescaze.
"Lord Algernon" etching, gift of Dwight Lanmon, 2013.
Norman House (#628) blueprints, gift of Abigail Norman, 2020.
Inventory
- Individual commissions
  Unnumbered projects are listed first, in order by date. Numbered projects are listed next, by project number. For an alphabetical listing, see Alphabetical index of projects at the end of this finding aid.
  - Unidentified projects
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 1)
      photographs (bookshelves, others), renderings (inkwell, sofa, desk lamp, "Project for Washington DC", others), sketches ("Elevation D’Une Paroi Laterale A L’Echelle 1/100/Juillet 1919," others), etc.
  - Unnumbered projects
    - 1200 Market St. [Philadelphia Savings Fund Society building?], undated; 3 blueprints [?], 1 photograph (Oversize 1)
    - CBS, unidentified projects, undated; photographs, drawings, renderings (Oversize 5)
    - Grand Central building, undated; 1 folio of drawings (Oversize 8)
    - Hanna building, Cleveland, OH, undated; 1 drawing, "Flower from Jones Russell" (Oversize 8)
    - Kootz residence, undated; 1 elevation and plan (Oversize 17)
    - League of Nations, undated; 1 rendering (Oversize 8)
    - Community House for La Chaux de Fonds, 1919 (Box 1)
    - Diploma Project, Large building block in Zurich [??], 1919; color drawing (Oversize 1)
    - Warehouse for the Board of Education, Cleveland, OH, 1922 (Box 1)
    - Edgewood School, 1924 (Box 1)
    - Painted drapery for a restaurant, 1924 (Box 1)
    - Country House for A Young Couple, commissioned for Architecture Forum, 1927; ink drawings; 3 site plans, 1 rendering (Oversize 17)
    - Soldiers and Sailors Monument, 1928
      - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
      - Drawings, 3 renderings (Oversize 11)
    - An American House, 1928 (Box 1)
    - Halle Brothers Exhibition, 1928 (Box 1)
    - House of the Future, 1928 (Box 1)
    - Barber and beauty shop, Grand Central Station, 1928 (Box 1)
    - Apartment house project, Park Avenue and 72nd Street, 1928, June; 2 renderings (Oversize 17)
    - Future American Country House, Commissioned for Architectural Record, 1928
      - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
      - Drawings, 2 renderings, enhanced with color (Oversize 1)
    - Maurice J. Speiser residence, Philadelphia, PA, 1933 [?] (Box 1)
    - House for Meridian Housing Corporation, 1936 (Box 1)
    - House of 2039 Project, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous unidentified photographs (Box 1)
  - 107B William Stix Wasserman residence, Whitemarsh, PA
    - Miscellaneous
    - Drawings, 6 renderings (Oversize 17)
  - 117 James M. R. Sinkler residence, Philadelphia, PA, 1 rendering (Oversize 17)
  - 121 Philadelphia Saving Fund Society main vault, Philadelphia, PA
    - Photographs, 2 photographs (Oversize 4)
    - Miscellaneous
  - 131 Simeon Ford House, 2 Sutton Square, NYC
    See also 771 William Brown Meloney alteration at Sutton Square, NYC.
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Photograph, 1 photograph (Oversize 8)
  - 133 Willow Garden Restaurant
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Photographs of screen, interior, 4 photographs (Oversize 8)
  - 157 Theatre and store building for Carl Brunson Hollywood, CA, 1926
  - 180 Tapestry design for theatre, New Haven, CT (Box 1)
  - 185 Moulin Rouge Restaurant alterations, NYC (Box 1)
  - 214 Alice Ferguson apartment house, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous
  - 220 Jean de Sieyes hunting lodge, Mt. Kisco, NY
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1 site plan, 2 renderings, 2 photographs (Oversize 2)
  - 222 R. Colfax Phillips apartment, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Drawing, 1 rendering (Oversize 1)
  - 226 Frederick Loeser Exhibition Rooms, Brooklyn (Box 1)
  - 228 Amos Parrish & Co. offices, NYC (Box 1)
  - 232 Macy exhibition, penthouse studio, NYC (Box 1)
  - 236 Nudelman & Conti showroom, NYC (Box 1)
  - 239 S. T. Meyer's apartment store, NYC (Box 1)
  - 241 Leopold Stokowski apartment, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Photographs, 1 photograph (Oversize 8)
  - 247 London Shoe showroom, NYC, drawings; 2 renderings/elevations (Oversize 8)
  - 251 Andrew Geller Shoe Stores showroom, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Drawings, 1 drawing, 1 rendering (Oversize 1)
  - 252 Apartment house and garage, West 50th and West 51st Streets, NYC, 1 rendering (“worm’s eye view”), 2 drawings (Oversize 2)
  - 255 Maison Bertie beauty parlor, NYC (Box 1)
  - 256 Arden Gallery penthouse duplex, NYC (Box 1)
  - 258 Oak Lane Country Day School, Philadelphia
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - Photographs, 2 photographs, 1 photo of drawing, 1 negative (Oversize 2)
    - Drawings, 1 site plan, 1 rendering (Oversize 2)
  - 259 Unity Lap Robe Co. showroom, NYC (Box 2)
  - 262 William Wasserman residence, 2 renderings (Box 2)
  - 270 Mrs. Charles Harding salon, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - Drawings, 2 renderings (Oversize 8)
  - 272 Briggs Haberdashery, NYC, 1 rendering (Oversize 1)
  - 275 Herbert M. Dreyfus apartment, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - Drawing (Oversize 8)
  - 276 Ben Herzberg apartment, NYC (Box 2)
  - 277 Mrs. George French Porter house, Ojai, CA
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - Drawing, 1 rendering (Oversize 17)
  - 284 Philadelphia Saving Fund Society Building, Philadelphia
    - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous
    - Drawings, renderings, sketches, etc. (Oversize 4)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
    - Photo panel, 1 item (Oversize 13)
    - Tracings, includes sections, layout of banking room floor, details of various portions of building including elevators, stairways, hardware, bank counters, mail chutes and mailboxes, doors, etc.; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Tracings, includes details of various portions of building including concession booth, telephone booth, lighting, pneumatic tube stations, kitchen, board room, dining room, elevator cabs, tellers' cages, steel grilles, dumbwaiters, clocks, signs, record cabinet, furniture, etc.; 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Tracings, includes plan, elevation and details of barber shop; elevations and sections of various portions of building; electrical layouts and outlet locations; details of windows, roof, ceilings, trolley wire connection; future squash court layout; proposed tenant storage; furniture layouts for various floors and rooms,; signage, ettering, color diagrams; plan for Trans-Lux Theatre; etc.; 7 folders (Box 4)
    - Tracings, includes floor plans for all floors including basement, furniture plans, designs for desks and tables, assorted signage, rattan furniture layout, board room furniture and decor, layouts for linen chest and silver safe, flagpoles, lettering and signage, and blueprints from Victor V. Clad Co. (kitchen), Curtiss Lighting (show windows and main space lighting), N. Smellenburg & Co. (rugs and carpets), American District Telegraph Co. (fire alarm box), Structural Waterproofing Co. (wall section); 8 folders (Box 5)
    - Tracings, includes typescript "Architectural Analysis of the Proposed Building for the Philadelphia Savings Fund Society at 12th and Market Streets" (1930), sectional plans and cross-sections for subway [?], street view profiles, structural plans for upper floors (7-17), presentation drawings for 5th and 22nd-32nd floors, sketches for light fixtures and desks, and details for stairs, doors, hall buttons, working spaces. Also includes material from Riggs, Distler & Co. (lavatories) and from Pringle Electrical Mfg. Co. (battery charging station, switchboards, etc.); 7 folders (Box 6)
    - Tracings, basement plan, sketches for lighting fixtures, rental brochure with color rendering and floor plan, structural and rental for floors 1, 3, 4, 5 and 6; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Photographs and articles (Box 8)
    - Book of construction photographs (Box 9)
  - 286 Arthur Peck house, Paoli, PA (Box 10)
  - 289 Howe and Lescaze office, Philadelphia
    - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Photographs, 2 photographs (Oversize 8)
  - 295 Museum of Modern Art project, NYC
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - "A Modern Museum" bound folio (Oversize 7)
  - 297 Philadelphia Saving Fund Society garage, Philadelphia, PA
    - Miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - Photographs, 4 photographs (Oversize 4)
  - 301 Frederick Vanderbilt Field house, New Hartford, CT
    - Miscellaneous, including photographs, photographs, negatives, tracings, blueprints; includes elevations, plans, plumbing and heating plans, framing, topographical details, electrical layouts, and details of closets, stairs, handrails, furniture, windows, lighting fixtures, shelving, etc.; 5 folders (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Photographs, 2 photographs, 1 photograph of rendering (Oversize 8)
    - Photo panels, 1 item (Oversize 13)
  - 304 Dartington Hall, headmaster's house (W. B. Curry), South Devon, England
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous
    - Photographs, 1 photograph (Oversize 3)
  - 304B Dartington Hall, junior school
  - 307 Trans Lux motion picture theaters, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - Drawings, 1 photograph, 3 renderings (Oversize 8)
  - 312 Hessian Hills School, Croton-on-Hudson, NY
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - Photographs, 1 photograph (Oversize 8)
  - 313 Frank Vance Storrs offices (Box 12)
  - 314 William Stix Wasserman office, Philadelphia (Box 12)
  - 316 Hattie Carnegie shop, 5 photogaphs (Oversize 8)
  - 318 Fox motion picture theater (Box 12)
  - 320 Pennsylvania Museum of Art children's room, Philadelphia, PA (Box 12)
  - 321 Maurice Wertheim house, Cos Cob, CT
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders
    - Drawings, 3 renderings (Oversize 2)
  - 322 Christie-Forsythe housing development, NYC
    - Miscellaneous, including photographs, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 13)
    - Drawings, 1 rendering (Oversize 2)
  - 323 Dartington Hall offices, South Devon, England (Box 14)
  - 335 Psi Upsilon Fraternity Club House, Dartmouth College, Hanover, NH (Box 14)
  - 336 River Gardens housing development, NYC
    - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Photostat plan enhanced with color (Oversize 12)
  - 339 Dorothy Gray store front, NYC (Box 14)
  - 340 Astoria-Queens housing development, NYC, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 345 Laurel Hill housing development, NYC
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Drawings, 3 renderings (Oversize 8)
  - 346 Churston Estate housing development, Devon, England
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous, including photographs, 6 folders (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous
    - Drawings, 1 rendering (Oversize 1)
    - Photographs, 1 photograph (Oversize 1)
  - 347 Dartington Hall boarding school, South Devon, England
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Photographs, 1 photograph (Oversize 3)
  - 355 Dartington Hall, nursery school, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 356 Dartington Hall, gymnasium
    - Miscellaneous, including photographs, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Drawing, 1 rendering (Oversize 1)
  - 357 Dartington Hall offices and laboratory
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous
    - Photographs, 1 photograph (Oversize 3)
  - 358 Dartington Hall piggery (Box 19)
  - 360 Roy F. Spreter house and garage/studio, Ardmore, PA
    - Miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1 drawing, 1 photograph, 1 photo rendering (Oversize 3)
  - 361 Dr. G. W. Hartmann house, State College, PA
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Drawing, 1 rendering (Oversize 2)
  - 364 Children's Haven hospital, NYC (Box 20)
  - 366 Wilbour Library alterations, Brooklyn (Box 20)
  - 369 Dartington Hall, cottages, South Devon, England
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous
  - 375 Dartington Hall, theater, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 377 Queensbridge housing development, NYC (Box 21)
  - 379 Raymond C. Kramer town house, 32 East 74th, NYC
    - Drawings (Tube 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous, including photographs, 5 folders (Box 22)
    - Photographs, 2 photographs (Oversize 3)
  - 380 William Kay Wallace country house, Bedford Village, NY (Box 22)
  - 381 Editorial Publications office alterations, NYC (Box 22)
  - 386 Brooklyn Children's Museum, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Drawings, 1 rendering (Oversize 8)
    - Miscellaneous
  - 387 Metropolitan Museum of Art - American Industrial Art Exhibition, NYC (Box 22)
  - 388 Williamsburg (Ten Eyck) housing project, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Project book, bound, contains photographs, plans, descriptions, etc. (Oversize 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1 rendering, 1 photograph (Oversize 11)
  - 391 Brooklyn Museum, auditorium, NYC
  - 393 Dartington Hall. Jooss residence, South Devon, England (Box 23)
  - 396 Mrs. Benjamin J. Buttenweiser town house, 17 East 73rd, NYC (Box 23)
  - 397 Unity House camp, Bushkill, PA
    See also Scrapbooks, Oversize 14.
    - Miscellaneous (I), blueprints, including bar layout, main building, refrigerator details, electrical and plumbing plans, sewage disposal, kitchen ventilation (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (II), blueprints, plans and sketches; includes plan for building A, front and rear elevations, sketch of exterior, and details for sewage disposal, stairs, lounge fireplace, piano hinge, "toilet room", telephone booths (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (III), includes contour map, survey, outdoor landscaping and tree positions, layouts A and B, tennis courts survey, mechanic plot, etc. (Box 23)
    - Photo album, 1935; progress photos of Unity House (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous (I), includes photographs of interior (fireplace, chairs, tables, stairwell, hallway, bar, dining hall, dormitory, etc.) and exterior (cottage, pavilion, entrance sign, etc.); photos taken during construction; a few negatives and black prints; articles from Architectural Record (1936) and New York Times (1965); sketches of tea room, dining room, lounge, deck (Box 24)
      Portfolio of Special Building Types (185-193)
    - Miscellaneous (II), includes plans for toilet room building, alterations to social hall, 8-room cottages (several different schemes); sketches of tennis courts, cottage plot plan, door details, shelving (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous (III), includes plans and elevations for Building #1 and dormitory, sketches of Building #1, room layouts, details of stair railing, windows, mirrors, shelves (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous (IV), material relating to Building A including survey of new roads, "1-0" and "1/8-0" sections, roof/floor/foundation, elevations, and details of casement windows, lounge fireplace, light trough, sliding doors, etc. (Box 24)
    - Photographs, dining room; 1 item (Oversize 8)
  - 398 CBS Theater, West 45th Street, NYC
    - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - Photographs (Oversize 5)
  - 402 Cocktail shaker design, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - 405 CBS Studios, 485 Madison Avenue, NYC (Box 25)
  - 406 Brunswick-Balke-Collender billiard tables, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - 407 Vincent K. Cates house, Melrose, MA (Box 25)
  - 408 J. Walter Thompson office for Ruth Waldo, NYC (Box 25)
  - 409 Howard Froelich house, NYC (Box 25)
  - 410 CBS little theater, NYC (Box 25)
  - 411 Silvray lamps (Box 25)
  - 417 CBS display room, NYC (Box 25)
  - 418 CBS miscellaneous accessories, NYC (Box 25)
  - 419 Ansonia High School, Ansonia, CT
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 8 folders (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous, including photographs, 4 folders (Box 27)
    - Photographs, 19 photographs (Oversize 3)
    - Miscellaneous
  - 426 CBS Studios, NYC, 3 folders (Box 28)
    Tracings: floor plans for 2, 3, 4, 6, 7, 8 and tower; elevations N, S and W
    Rough drafts and sketches for several schemes (uncounted)
    Blueprints for Scheme 30 (9 pg. dated 12/15/1935, includes 1st fl, 1st fl mezzanine, 1st fl deck, 2nd fl mezzanine, promenade roof, typical office floor 2d-5th, street elevation, avenue elevation), Scheme 33 (8 pg. dated 2/16/1936, includes summary, 1st fl, 2d fl, 2d fl mezzanine, 4th fl, 6th fl, 7-12th fl), and Scheme 39 (8 pg. dated 7/13/1936, includes stores, 2d fl, 3d fl, 4th fl, 4th fl mezzanine, typical office floor, elevation)
    Unlabeled prints, some damaged (31 items)
    Items from other jobs, including 110 E. 59th St (photostat copy, 1 item), Liederkranz Hall, 115 E. 58th St. (6 tracings), and an apartment house at 485 Park Ave (4 drawings and 3 photostats)
  - 431 CBS microphones, NYC
    See also 751 CBS microphones.
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Scrapbook (Oversize 5)
  - 432 Lloyd Good and William Butler weekend houses, Harvey Cedars, NJ (Box 28)
  - 434 Purdue University small house, Purdue, IN (Box 28)
  - 440 Magnolia Petroleum exposition building, Dallas, Texas
    - Miscellaneous (Box 28)